[{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974997546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":19871,"timeElapsed":140580},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975005009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":7460,"timeElapsed":148044},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975016160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":11147,"timeElapsed":159195},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975026517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":10353,"timeElapsed":169552},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975031024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4504,"timeElapsed":174059},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975037846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6819,"timeElapsed":180881},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975040174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2324,"timeElapsed":183209},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975056595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":16418,"timeElapsed":199630},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975062915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6316,"timeElapsed":205950},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975079653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":15017,"timeElapsed":222688},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975085790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":6134,"timeElapsed":228825},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975090111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4318,"timeElapsed":233146},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975092469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2355,"timeElapsed":235504},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975096174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3703,"timeElapsed":239209},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975099264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3087,"timeElapsed":242299},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975101885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2618,"timeElapsed":244920},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975106883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4996,"timeElapsed":249918},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975111215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4329,"timeElapsed":254250},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975122280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9917,"timeElapsed":265315},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975125031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2748,"timeElapsed":268066},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975127758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2724,"timeElapsed":270793},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975129712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1952,"timeElapsed":272747},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975135833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6119,"timeElapsed":278868},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975138858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3022,"timeElapsed":281893},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975140967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2106,"timeElapsed":284002},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975144940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3971,"timeElapsed":287975},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975147196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2253,"timeElapsed":290231},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975155959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7447,"timeElapsed":298994},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975158459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2498,"timeElapsed":301494},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975161159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2697,"timeElapsed":304194},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975163048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1886,"timeElapsed":306083},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975168003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4953,"timeElapsed":311038},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975170986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2980,"timeElapsed":314021},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975173435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2447,"timeElapsed":316470},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975178374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4936,"timeElapsed":321408},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975181031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2654,"timeElapsed":324066},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975191841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":9557,"timeElapsed":334876},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975196986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5144,"timeElapsed":340021},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975200220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3231,"timeElapsed":343255},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975203285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3062,"timeElapsed":346320},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975205864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2576,"timeElapsed":348899},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975209082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3216,"timeElapsed":352117},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975212285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3200,"timeElapsed":355320},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975215446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3159,"timeElapsed":358481},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975217738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2290,"timeElapsed":360773},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975229821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":10846,"timeElapsed":372856},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975231122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1298,"timeElapsed":374157},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975242515,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11390,"timeElapsed":385550},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975247930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5413,"timeElapsed":390965},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975250199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2266,"timeElapsed":393234},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975253109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2907,"timeElapsed":396144},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975255149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2037,"timeElapsed":398184},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975257427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2276,"timeElapsed":400462},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975261077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3647,"timeElapsed":404112},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975262880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1800,"timeElapsed":405915},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975271304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":7203,"timeElapsed":414339},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975273108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1800,"timeElapsed":416143},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975274908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1798,"timeElapsed":417943},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975276822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":419857},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975279372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2548,"timeElapsed":422407},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975280874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1499,"timeElapsed":423909},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975282587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":425621},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975284471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":1882,"timeElapsed":427506},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975286877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2404,"timeElapsed":429912},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975293242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5141,"timeElapsed":436276},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975294983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":438018},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975296616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1630,"timeElapsed":439651},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975298973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2355,"timeElapsed":442008},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975302225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3250,"timeElapsed":445260},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975304652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2425,"timeElapsed":447687},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975307433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2778,"timeElapsed":450468},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975309988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2553,"timeElapsed":453023},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975311776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1786,"timeElapsed":454811},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975316518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3625,"timeElapsed":459553},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975320550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4029,"timeElapsed":463585},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975322673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2121,"timeElapsed":465708},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975324414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":467449},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975326178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1762,"timeElapsed":469213},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975329547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3366,"timeElapsed":472582},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975331494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":1945,"timeElapsed":474529},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975334015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":477050},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975338699,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4681,"timeElapsed":481734},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975343969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":5268,"timeElapsed":487004},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975355729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":10550,"timeElapsed":498764},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975358210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2478,"timeElapsed":501245},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975359712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1500,"timeElapsed":502747},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975361318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1603,"timeElapsed":504353},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975364391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3071,"timeElapsed":507426},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975366383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1990,"timeElapsed":509418},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975372546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6161,"timeElapsed":515581},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975374678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2130,"timeElapsed":517713},{"subjectID":"ols9ghdfzx","prolificID":"669dade6ddbc6f0b20ce3786","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d750ed2255e6a3b7673","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975376760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2079,"timeElapsed":519795}]